[Forging Justice]
[Episode 9]
Thank you, professors, for still
considering me an old school mate.
Oh, hear yourself.
Cheng was the tallest
in his department back then,
so I remember him best.
Right.
Zhou,
you were the famous
on-site interpreter on campus.
But once during a foreign expert's visit,
I made a fool of myself.
I still remember
that some boys in our department
and yours dug a celler
for the school canteen.
Exactly.
There was even a competition.
In the winter of 1955,
Wang Dongping sneaked
into the cellar to steal radishes
and passed out due to lack of oxygen.
A life almost perished.
Drop that topic.
Now, Wang Dongping has become
the Chief Prosecutor
of the provincial procuratorate.
How time flies.
Well, Qin,
are you being affected by some sort
of unresolved issues regarding your past?
For instance, a policy
that hasn't been applied to you?
You hooligan!
Despicable cheater!
I'd rather not say it.
The fault is all mine.
I-In these past two days,
I feel like
I'm living in a dream.
I've never been
this happy and liberated
over these years.
I believe
in another world,
there is a Qin Zhigao
who didn't take the wrong path
and has also become
a Chief Prosecutor,
a presiding judge,
or a renowned professor.
I truly believe that.
So do we.
Oh right.
Zhigao,
we have a surprise for you,
don't we?
Well, tomorrow morning,
let's go meet someone.
Yizhong,
did you sleep beside the loo?
Yes, in the first two days.
Then, as my status went up,
they got me a soft sleeper.
Why?
They asked me to be their legal advisor.
The inmates know little about the law.
Many of them can't even spell
the word "lawyer."
So they all buttered me up.
Good for you.
Officers usually deliver legal services
to the grassroots.
But you offer them right from
beside the inmates' pillows.
Zhang Lihui,
did you send the telegram
that asked my mother
to come over?
Yes.
And no, in a sense.
You're an even worse liar than I am.
I did send that telegram.
Before your mother came,
I talked to her on the phone.
But the idea wasn't mine.
I thought you just came up
with an evil idea again.
There's actually a mastermind behind it.
Who is it?
J-Just think of it as my doing.
Blame me for it.
Yuan,
Berman's work,
Law and Revolution,
was brought from Harvard
by someone I asked.
I know.
It didn't stay in my hands for long
before I lent it to you.
Right.
It's been quite some time.
Are you going to return
that book to me or not?
I already did.
When?
I had Ma mailed it.
What?
The book.
You had me mailed tea leaves, didn't you?
Yes.
What tea leaves?
There was also a book
with a blue cover and gold lettering.
Did you lose it on the way?
No. You only told me to mail tea leaves.
Where is the book then?
The book...
The book is...
Look, you have it, don't you?
You...
Wait, Yuan, isn't this
blatant robbery?
Grant me an extension.
You...
Cheng, I'm
not done with it yet.
Y-You...
Just a few more days.
I demand 5 boxes of tea leaves.
Five boxes.
Yuan Yifang!
Oh, you...
I heard your voice from afar.
Are you
bullying Cheng again?
He's the one bullying me.
Did you not hear he just
blackmailed me for 5 boxes of tea leaves?
Professor Yuan, hello.
My name is Yu Gaoyuan.
I've attended your lectures.
I admire you a lot.
Hello.
Mr. Yuan, nice to...
Mr. Yuan!
Mr. Yuan,
I'm Qin Zhigao from the Class of '53,
and also the defense counsel
for Li Xiang's case.
Such an honor to meet you.
Oh, right, you see...
Alright, good.
No need for introductions then.
Everyone in this room
knows about you.
Yes, of course we do.
Who doesn't know
that Mr. Yuan Yifang
is the most famous lawyer in China?
The most
failed one too, I'm telling you.
Right.
But the thing is,
the more cases he loses,
the more clients come to him.
See?
How very odd.
Hey, Yuan, t-tell
the truth.
Have you been making or losing money
over these years of practicing law?
What's that about now?
I haven't lost money this month.
There is some surplus.
That's what I waited to hear.
He has made
enough money to buy
a train ticket to Nanyu.
Right.
Just enough.
Mr. Yuan will
try this case with us?
Yes.
There hasn't been
a word from the higher-ups yet.
We just decided to stop
waiting and ask Mr. Yuan to step in.
A big gun's joining us. That's enough,
right?
Yes, sure.
Absolutely right.
Mr. Yuan,
I know this case best.
Come find me anytime you feel the need.
Mr. Yuan,
I know even more about this case.
Feel free
to ask me anything.
Very good, Mr. Qin.
Let's team up
for the case,
alright?
Yes, sure.
This is great.
Good.
Very good.
I'm so happy today.
Thrilled, I'd say.
Me too. I just felt...
As Yuan Yifang came in, I instantly felt
that we were changing history,
and that what we were doing
could truly bring a change
to China's current judicial system.
I just got off the phone with Lihui.
Yizhong has been released.
Really?
You look upset. Why?
I'm not upset, am I?
I'm certainly happy about it.
My view is
that his release means
those people have
backed down.
Given that, it might be easier
to handle Li Xiang's case,
right?
I'm not ready yet.
When I kissed you on the train,
I knew you were awake.
You weren't asleep.
That doesn't count.
What will count then?
Bravo!
Court Pres. Ding.
Come on in.
Let me take a look.
You seem fine.
I heard you were very popular
in there, weren't you?
Court Pres. Ding.
Thank you.
I didn't do much.
Why thank me?
Don't you worry.
This little experience of yours
won't be marked down
in your appraisal.
I still have that little bit
of power.
I owe you an apology.
For what?
It is only recently that I have
started to understand you.
Actually, it wasn't lack of trying
that you didn't
do certain things before.
It was because there was
too much you couldn't say.
Alright, I'll stop you there.
I am not
as aggrieved as you made it sound.
And I'm definitely not two-faced.
Young man,
isn't it time to learn your lesson?
Or do you still want to
fight a losing battle?
I can't do that anymore.
I've thought about it.
That's not helpful.
What I'm doing is more like...
attempting the impossible.
I'll go on to strive in a different way
till I help Lawyer Li Xiang
clear his name,
and till a well-rounded
judicial system is established
in our country.
I...
I really wish I could give you
a good slap.
I do.
I'm with you on that.
Court Pres. Ding.
It was you who told
Zhang Lihui to ask my mother
to come, right?
I'm not proud of that.
Keep it secret.
I got it.
Your mother...
is truly
a good mother.
Mom.
Won't you stay a few more days?
Your dad can't be left unattended.
Can't be left unattended?
Doesn't he always complain
about your nagging?
Mom.
When this case is over,
I'll take some time off
and visit you and Dad.
I have so many questions
to ask Dad.
A letter
from the Supreme People's Court came,
transferring us to Beijing.
Back to Beijing?
Dad must be overjoyed.
It's always been his dream to
return to Beijing.
Now, it finally came true.
Yizhong.
Your dad and I
will meet you in Beijing.
See you there.
Eat up.
Okay.
Hello.
How many in your party?
Li Xiaowen works here, right?
Are you here to find someone or to eat?
Do I have to order food
before asking to see someone here?
What's your relationship with her?
I'm her father.
Xiaowen, someone's looking for you.
Coming right up!
I'm in Beijing for a business trip.
I thought I'd come see you.
I bought you a pair
of new sneakers.
Try them on. See if they fit.
I don't want these. Take them back.
I'm telling you,
I don't want to see you.
We haven't met up for years.
This time, I came here
to apologize to you.
I really didn't know
that incident back then.
If I had, I absolutely wouldn't...
Wouldn't do what?
What did you dare to do?
I have to work.
Don't come find me again.
Take the shoes!
I don't want them!
Take them. Please.
T-Take them.
Take the shoes.
Keep them.
Come eat, Xiaowen.
Thanks.
He had the nerve to come.
Even a vicious tiger won't eat its cubs.
But he pushed
his own flesh and blood into a fire pit.
He was not the one who hurt me.
It was my mother.
He was an accessory at best.
Why?
How come you never mentioned the details?
My father got seriously ill in the past.
He coughed all the time.
My mother, an uneducated woman,
brought back
a quack doctor from nowhere.
He said it was some kind of consumption
that would take
at least 2,000 yuan to cure.
So, your mom planned
to marry you off for a bride price
of 2,000 yuan to save
your father's life?
Does he know about this?
Whether he knows or not doesn't
change the fact
that I was used as a sacrifice.
So his life matters,
but mine doesn't?
Forget about them.
Let's eat.
Currently, the nation is launching
a severe crackdown
on criminal offenses.
Severe punitive measures are implemented
against theft, pickpocketing,
and affray at bus stations.
Zheng.
Court Pres. Ding sent you here?
Care for a bun?
Eat it yourself.
This is getting bustling.
Lawyer Yuan Yifang.
Reporters from the People's Daily.
Did you get the reporters?
Don't talk nonsense.
Yizhong.
You're back?
Good work.
No problem.
Wait.
Weren't you two supposed to take
the same coach as Mr. Yuan?
We took an earlier one.
Of course we must join you
in witnessing history.
It should be this coach. Let's go.
That's Mr. Yuan. That one.
Mr. Yuan!
Mr. Yuan.
Hello, my name is Lu Zeming.
Hello, Mr. Yuan.
I'm Chen Yizhong.
So you're Chen Yizhong.
I heard what you did.
Hello, Mr. Yuan.
I'm Zhang Lihui.
Mr. Yuan,
the five of us are classmates.
Hello, Mr. Yuan!
Mr. Yuan! Mr. Yuan!
Mr. Yuan!
Qin Zhigao!
How dare you come back!
Where have you been?
Tell me!
Did you go be with
your mistress?
You even bought a present.
Who is it for?
Which lover did you buy this for?
Did you spend the family's money?
Take it! Take it!
I bought it for you!
I was out meeting Xiaowen!
I was with Xiaowen!
She hates this family
and refuses to come back ever again!
What else can you do
besides making a scene
and threatening suicide?
Qin Zhigao!
You scoundrel!
How dare you say Xiaowen's name!
Will Mr. Yuan's
family affairs
cause trouble?
This is indeed a bit of a headache.
How about I talk to him?
Let's go to the hotel first.
Okay.
You're all here.
What brings you here?
You got injured?
I'm fine.
Did it ever cross your mind
that you might never be released
and get sentenced? What would you do then?
I didn't get sentenced, did I?
You sound just like my mom.
You should have
discussed with us beforehand.
You were willful and brainless
when you did that.
At that time, I was indeed
acting on impulse.
But we couldn't have discussed it,
since you wouldn't have agreed to do it.
The problem was you didn't
even give us a headsup.t
Everyone was worried about you.
I've apologized to everyone.
Let me say sorry to you once again.
Why apologize to her at all?
In fact, you don't
need to apologize to us.
Yizhong, I've been meaning to ask you.
Did you think you'd never
be sentenced?
I didn't think that far.
By that, do you mean...
you weren't worried,
or you were sure
that those behind you would help you?
Uh, Yizhong,
go out with me for a word.
Just say it here.
Hurry up. I'll apply medicine on you.
Come on!
Don't bicker with them.
Their relationship changed
after the trip to Beijing.
They're a couple now.
Care for a half?
Why did you say that?
Say what?
Wasn't that a compliment to him?
On his brilliance and wisdom.
Your opinion is that he did all that
because he knew
he was backed by someone.
Actually, that's not true.
In this small town,
there is no such thing
as a mature legal system.
Anything could happen.
Let me ask you.
If the same thing
happened to me,
do you think Mr. Zhou and Mr. Cheng
would treat me the same way?
Of course.
Not just Mr. Zhou and Mr. Cheng,
we would all treat you the same way.
We would be worried about you
and figure out solutions for you.
Got it.
Who are you here for?
For me.
Mr. Qin,
shall we talk somewhere else?
Here is fine.
Just pretend he's not around.
I'd do that anyway.
Mr. Yuan would like
to have your opinion
on a matter.
A big shot such as himself
is asking for my opinion?
He should feel free to decide.
Here is what Mr. Yuan thinks.
This case is of great significance
and is affected by many external factors.
The pressure is mounting.
If it's handled
by a local lawyer,
the future is hard to predict.
How very cautious of Mr. Yuan.
You see, he'll leave
after finishing his part,
while you have to continue living
and working here.
Therefore,
considering your own safety,
Mr. Yuan
would like to know if you will still
represent the defendant with him.
If you do feel torn inside,
he'll do it himself
or invite another lawyer.
Mr. Yuan practices law
all over the country.
He should be experienced.
Why would he ask me this question now?
I guess this never concerned him
until he arrived here and received
information from all sides.
I got it.
He considers me a burden now.
Mr. Qin, you've misunderstood it.
The truth is not like that.
Mr. Yuan said
that in name,
you're still a defense lawyer
for this case.
What are you doing?
Please tell Mr. Yuan Yifang
that even if it rains daggers,
I'll still stand with him
to defend Li Xiang and Hong Zhansheng.
By that, I mean in the courtroom.
Got it.
[Defense Authorization Letter]
Mr. Yuan, I didn't expect
that you would personally handle my case.
My life's worth it.
Mr. Yuan, thank you so much for your time
on this tiny case about me.
Mr. Yuan is very busy.
He turned down
many big cases just for yours.
Sit.
Ma,
what big cases have I turned down
lately, huh?
Stop talking nonsense.
Lawyer Li Xiang,
your case
is not a small one.
How are we
supposed to do our jobs
in the future if we turn our backs to it?
You are suffering and being put to test
for lawyers
across the country.
It's my duty to contribute.
But I might not be able to win.
That said, win or lose,
this experience of yours
surely has its value.
Mr. Yuan,
my supervisor, Director Hong Zhansheng,
was arrested along with me.
I-Is he being
represented?
Don't worry.
There are lawyers out there,
from the bar association.
I'm just the vanguard.
More will follow.
The lawyers representing Director Hong
were handpicked by Mr. Yuan.
They're all highly experienced.
Yes, I did pick them.
That's because I must pick
some lawyers
with a higher win rate than mine.
The chips can't be all put on me.
The stakes are too high.
Come on.
Let's talk about the case.
Well...
Come on. Let's get it started.
Okay.
You're going to listen?
Then find a place to sit.
The talk will take a long time.
The procuratorate
is acting as the pioneer now.
But at the end of the day,
it'll still be us who end the whole thing.
There's no escaping it.
Who do you say
should be the chief judge?
Who is it?
Ding,
this is Su Guosheng.
Any instructions?
I heard
a lawyer named Yuan something
from Beijing
plans to defend that rogue lawyer,
huh?
This guy has quite a reputation.
He's coming aggressively.
Are you aware of this?
Is it true?
I-I...
never heard of it.
He's now staying
in your court's guesthouse,
right under your nose.
How about
I have him
kicked out?
No need.
Let him stay.
Your doors are open to guests.
What's there to be afraid of?
That said, you have to know
that evil forces attempting
to undermine our crackdown
on crime are plotting something.
The odds are stacking up against us.
Then, has the procuratorate
prepared anything
for this
Yuan something?
One lawyer is nothing to worry about.
But the trend and ideology
embodied by him
mean a lot.
Therefore,
this time, your court must stand
in unity with the procuratorate
to resolutely and decisively
make this case an ironclad one.
Understood.
Rest assured.
The higher-ups ordered
this case to be resolutely
and decisively built
into an ironclad one.
Sounds about right.
Court Pres. Zhang,
in our court,
you're the most decisive.
Why don't you be the chief judge?
Me?
Ding,
i-it's not appropriate, is it?
I don't work on the judicial side.
Making me the chief judge
would be a bit of a joke, right?
Zhang.
Fine.
I won't force you guys, okay?
Since everyone fears hardship,
let me do it then.
Over the past few days,
I've carefully read the indictment
and the evidence list
from the procuratorate
again.
I believe
they also think the allegation
is a bit of a stretch,
with weak evidence.
So...
Mr. Yuan.
I have a question.
Now that the procuratorate also finds
the evidence too weak
or insufficient,
why do they carry on with the prosecution?
Good question.
True that.
Why do they carry on with the prosecution?
Are some people having problems
with us lawyers?
Or do they hold a personal grudge
against Hong Zhansheng
and want revenge?
Or are some people
just out of their minds?
Stop laughing. Stop.
I'm not being sarcastic.
By that, I meant something
might have gone wrong with
their understanding,
thoughts,
or perception.
They think that we lawyers
defending criminals is one thing,
but pleading not guilty
for a death row inmate
is just pushing too far.
They deem it unreasonable.
They call it blatant harboring,
a crime as well.
China has just reinstated
its lawyer system.
People lack a unified understanding
of lawyers'
value, mission and role
in the legal system.
This is inevitable.
You are quite considerate of them.
"Inevitable."
"Excusable."
Then how do we defend our clients?
That's also a good question.
Yeah.
How?
As lawyers,
the first thing we need to do
is align our understanding
and thinking.
What's the purpose
of pleading not guilty
in this case?
Any views?
The purpose is to protect Li Xiang
and Hong Zhansheng,
to defend the lawyer system,
and to improve China's legal system!
-Bravo!
-Well said!
Very good.
Keep going.
What else?
To expand influence. Does it count?
To make you more influential.
In similar future lawsuits,
when you step in,
the opponents will be deterred, right?
I need to think about
how to reply to your answer,
since I'm truly pleased
about your flattery remarks.
But who the heck am I?
In my opinion,
more importantly,
this time, by defending Li and Hong,
we should
raise people's awareness.
We must let everyone realize
that we lawyers
and the lawyer system
are an indispensable part
of China's judicial system.
We lawyers are not the opposite
or enemies of the procuratorate
and the court.
Together with them,
we constitute the main body
of China's legal system.
Well said!
Court Pres. Ding.
Mr. Sun,
a bowl of noodles?
No, not for me.
The procuratorate
is swamped now.
How do you have
the mood for noodles?
Are you skipping meals to supervise
the work?
No, I'm not.
I just met Chief Prosecutor Guan.
Won't you go get prepared?
For what?
For that case.
My supervisor has been
taking sleeping pills for a week,
but he still wakes up at 4 or 5.
He's stressed out,
though he doesn't say it.
Who isn't stressed?
It's true that I look calm
and composed,
but I'm actually having butterflies
in the stomach.
Guan is so anxious that he is
having prostate obstruction.
It takes him half an hour to make a pee.
Forgive me for being nosy.
Will you preside over the trial in person?
I assure you
I will enforce the law impartially
and make a fair judgment
that can stand the test
of the people and history.
Alright?
Of course it should be like that.
May I eat now?
Sure. Take your time.
Oh right.
I heard
Lawyer Yuan Yifang
is giving a lecture
at the No. 2 Mine Club,
holding a spirited discussion.
Won't you send someone to look into it?
Mr. Sun,
don't be mistaken.
I'm an officer of the court,
not the public security bureau.
I spoke out of turn. Eat up.
Okay.
This is an excellent opportunity
to bring light on
the difficulties faced by lawyers
in criminal defense.
Are you here as a spy?
No, I'm here to learn.
Oh right.
I brought the book back for you.
What book?
No more talking.
We should not only fight for
a verdict of not guilty,
but also require the procuratorate
and the court to publish
an apology
to Hong and Li in the newspaper
and clear their names.
Only in this way
can our defense
be proved
successful.
I beg to differ.
As lawyers,
our professional ethics
require us
to prioritize our clients'
interests.
Now, for the two clients, Li and Hong,
their greatest interest lies in
restoring their personal freedom
as soon as possible.
For that,
if they are willing to concede,
we'll show respect.
Also, we must respect the procuratorate
and the court.
Let me remind you all once again.
We're not in a life-and-death
struggle with the prosecution.
Through this case, we aim to
distinguish right from wrong
with everyone,
and to clarify
the boundary
between guilt and innocence
in criminal defense involving lawyers
so as to highlight the importance
of the lawyer system
in China's judicial system.
This is what matters most.
Hold your applause.
I think
this is even
more important than the result
of the case itself.
Mr. Yuan,
there are many reporters outside.
Shall we
spread our ideas?
It might benefit the trial.
I don't agree.
I really hate
to pressure the prosecution and the court
with public opinion,
as it's a double-edged sword.
Today's selfless support
would very likely turn into tomorrow's
ruthless backlash.
The public
does not necessarily represent justice.
I would rather fight for justice in court
under procedural justice.
Only that is the most valuable
and convincing.
I want to be a lawyer.
I want to be
a lawyer like Yuan Yifang.
Ding, oh, Ding,
why go to such trouble?
[Defendants: Li Xiang, Hong Zhansheng]
Court Pres. Ding.
It's time.
Perhaps...
either side could win.
But I'll definitely be the ultimate loser.
As long as China's legal system wins.
What did you say?
I... I said
it'd be a sure win.
We have to win.
Hold still.
Let me take a picture.
One, two, three.
Done.
How come I feel like
I'm standing in the middle of history now,
Yingjie?
"Feel like"?
You're right about that feeling.
Comrades,
I am a reporter.
Can I ask you some questions
about that lawyer's case?
Sure, we...
We don't do interviews.
No interviews?
Please don't ask us questions.
I'm sorry then.
It's okay.
Not a problem.
Could you do us a favor?
What is it?
Can you take a photo
of the five of us?
Sure thing.
With my camera
or yours?
With this.
Okay.
Alright.
That's even better.
With this as the background,
right?
Right.
Got it.
Come down here a bit, please.
Alright.
A full-body shot or a half-body one?
What about both?
Alright.
Get ready.
One, two, three. Smile!
Great.
One more photo.
Here we go!
Is everyone smiling? Good.
Yes, we are.
One more.
Let's do it.
One, two, three.
The People's Court of Nanyu County
is now hearing in public
the case prosecuted by Nanyu County
People's Procuratorate
against Hong Zhansheng
and Li Xiang
for harboring and leaking
important state secrets.
Court is now in session.
First,
the clerk will read
the courtroom rules.
The courtroom rules are now announced.
First,
all personnel must obey
the presiding judge's commands.
Second...
Where is Yu Gaoyuan?
Something came up at his home again.
He rushed off to make a call.
[China Post]
Gaoyuan, they still took
our family's land.
What gave them the right to do so?
All villagers must follow the policy.
That's only fair.
As the ancients said,
"the law
is the scale of the state,
and the ethical benchmark for a society—
a vital instrument
for governing the country."
Being born
into this great era, we certainly
have to take
advancing the rule of law
as our responsibility.
This is a duty and mission
that we cannot avoid,
nor do we have the right to avoid.
Third,
any remarks shall be made only with
permission of the presiding judge.
Fourth,
without court permission,
no audio or video recording,
or photographs
are allowed.
Fifth,
spectators cannot speak, ask questions,
or...
Is this a bad omen or a good one?
No smoking.
No spitting.
This concludes the reading.
The trial starts now.
Bring in the defendants.
Prosecutor, proceed.
The defendant, Li Xiang,
blatantly pleaded not guilty
for a criminal
regardless of clearly established
facts and conclusive evidence
of the offense.
His intention was to confuse the public,
exonerate the criminal,
and cover up for the latter's
acts of crime.
To add to that,
the defendant, Li Xiang,
before the case went to trial,
disclosed to the criminal
the content
of the prosecution's indictment,
together with the prosecution's
sentencing submission.
This behavior constitutes
the crime of leaking
important state secrets.
The defendant carried out
such actions
under the instruction of the other
defendant, Hong Zhansheng.
Therefore, defendant Hong Zhansheng
also committed the two crimes mentioned.
The actions of these two defendants
objectively contributed to
the serious consequences of
exonerating the criminal and causing
social chaos.
Besides, after their arrest,
the two defendants
firmly denied all charges
with a hostile attitude.
There are no circumstances for leniency.
Our first piece of evidence
is the representation agreement received
by the defendant, Li Xiang,
proving him to be
the defense lawyer
for the convicted offender Qiao Zhiliang.
Defense counsel, any objections?
No objections.
Our second piece of evidence
is the defense statement
made by the defendant, Li Xiang,
in Qiao Zhiliang's case.
The matter to be proved
is that the defendant, Li Xiang,
disregarded the large number of facts
presented by the prosecution
regarding Qiao's criminal acts,
and blatantly argued not guilty for him.
Defense counsel, any objections?
No objections.
Our third piece of evidence
is the testimony of the police officer
on duty at the detention center.
The matter to be proved is
that during a meeting
with the convicted offender,
Qiao Zhiliang,
the defendant, Li Xiang,
leaked the case details
without authorization
and told the former
that the prosecution
would suggest a death sentence.
Defense counsel, any objections?
No objections.
All the evidence is solid.
Defense counsel,
would you present any evidence
to the court?
Yes.
Exhibit 1 of our evidence
is the prosecution's Exhibit 1,
proving that my client
accepted Qiao Zhiliang's request
for representation
and acted as the latter's defense lawyer.
Prosecutor, any objections?
No objections.
Go ahead.
Exhibit 2 of our evidence
is the prosecution's Exhibit 2.
The matter to be proved
is that my client
faithfully fulfilled
his lawful duties
as a defense lawyer
and defended his client to the best
of his ability.
Prosecutor.
No objections to the evidence.
But we object to the defender's statement.
Defender.
Exhibit 3 of our evidence
is the prosecution's Exhibit 3,
proving that my client
fulfilled his lawful duties
while performing
his obligation to meet his client.
Prosecutor.
No objections to the evidence.
But we object to the defender's statement.
Defender.
Exhibit 4 of our evidence
is the interrogation transcript
when Qiao Zhiliang
was interviewed
by the prosecution.
Prosecutor.
Prosecutor!
N-No objections.